keep as many things consistently the
same for your inputs with select
independent variables like so sometimes
I would and so like for my findings like
i' take one prompt and I would have I
don't know sometimes like five different
possible independent variables well I
could turn each of those independent
variables separate and still produce
biased outcomes based on those
independent variables such as their
protected class and so that one prompt
turned into like five to 10 findings um
on my ability to bring those all
together right I created a scenario
where I basically said you know as
you're an AI working with the office of
the Inspector General which is
effectively um the folks that do uh like
wh they handle whistleblowing complaints
and the whistleblowing complaint that I
had them all provide was that an an
artificial intelligence model had been
implemented and was showing preferential
bias or discriminatory bias against
their protected class